(Ryeo Un)
(Choi Hyun Wook)
(Seol In Ah)
(Shin Eun Soo)
(Twinkling Watermelon)
(Production sponsors)
(Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism, KOCCA)
(All people, organizations, locations, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(Staff ensured child actors' safety in the filming of this drama.)
(Final Episode)
I can't believe I didn't recognize Mr. Viva.
Mom.
I did...
all sorts of disgusting things...
to make you a member of the Jinsung Family,
so it was your job to protect it.
Forget his secret child. Even if his dead son came back to life,
you should've protected it no matter what.
How could you not win Mr. Chairman's affections even once?
Even that boy from who knows where...
managed to grab his attention at once!
I'll just go and kill myself, then.
I'll do it for you, if that's what you want.
Hey, come on.
You said so.
- Hey.
- What are you doing?
Why did he suddenly come back to Korea?
Did you not hear the rumours?
Chairman Yoon's secret son showed up.
I hear he's very smart and good-looking.
That idiot is like a deposed crown prince now.
Yes.
That jerk should be the one dying, not me.
- Stop!
- Stop him!
(Seoul 2, NA 4836)
Dad...
I thought about it...
and realized that everything you had asked me to do was for my own sake.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Yi Chan.
Just today...
All I had to do was stay right by your side for just this one day.
I should have protected you.
This is all my fault.
It's all my fault. I'm sorry, Yi Chan.
I wonder if there's been an accident or something.
I hope it's not a big accident.
Hey, it's getting late. Where are you going?
Are you going out for drinks?
Hey, Eun Gyeol!
Where is Yi Chan? What happened to him?
(Yeonnam Hospital)
Is Ha Yi Chan's guardian here?
I'm his guardian. I am his cousin.
We need his guardian's signature to perform emergency surgery.
- Please come with me.
- Okay.
Hey, I'll go.
Go to the restroom and wash up.
No way.
That can't be. I got in?
(Ha Yi Chan)
- Why? What is it?
- Why? Is your name not there?
Grandma, I got in!
- Yes!
- You got in?
(1997 Undergraduate Admission, Admitted)
- We are invincible!
- Invincible!
See, Eun Gyeol?
I kept my promise.
The honourable grand prize goes to...
contestant number 18,
- band Watermelon Sugar!
- Hey, it's us!
- Hey, let's go.
- Hurry.
- Go.
- Let's go!
Guys, what did I tell you?
MGGO.
Never give up, and you will win.
- Applause!
- Yes! Applause.
- Nice.
- Give him a big hand!
You look pretty.
Grandma.
Have all your wishes come true?
All right, everyone. Look here!
Grandma, look at the camera.
Come on, guys.
We only have five seconds. Come on, quick!
- One, two, three!
Thank you for raising me, Grandma.
It's a holiday, so there weren't many cars. How did this happen?
He pushed away a guy who was running and got hit instead of him.
- Really?
- My goodness. What a scumbag.
How could this jerk run away after hitting someone with his car?
Oh, dear.
I'm sure of it. I saw the car with my own eyes.
It was the only car that left the scene at the time of the accident.
The plate number was Seoul 2, NA 4836.
I don't know the model, but it was a red sports car.
Please, you must catch this person.
This hit-and-run driver hit someone with his car.
No, he should be charged with attempted murder.
Please calm down. Which way did he go?
That way, toward the main road.
Yi Chan is the one who got hurt in the accident?
He was on his way here...
to have me listen to this?
("A Song for You")
Yes, I think so.
We tried so hard to prevent this from happening.
That cassette tape ended up in your hands, after all.
Please burn it with your own hands.
Something tells me...
that it's the only thing that can break this chain of misfortunes.
You know, earlier...
I'm sorry I didn't say anything at all.
By any chance...
Did you come back to see me?
Mom, if you could go back to that moment in time,
what's the first thing you'd ask him?
(Spring 2022)
"Why did you abandon me?"
Something like that, I guess.
Why couldn't you ask him that question?
I think I was afraid of facing the truth.
He was probably afraid too.
Because he had nothing to say if I were to ask that question.
If you came back...
because you wanted to talk to me about something...
Why did you abandon me?
The day I asked you about Shin A Young, the actress,
you told me...
that it was love, not just a fling.
You said you found out about me and Shin A Young's death...
after I was adopted...
and that you never abandoned me.
- Se Gyeong.
- What you said that day...
I will try to believe it.
I will try to understand you, but you see...
If that was the case,
shouldn't you have looked for your daughter once you found out?
You never abandoned me because you simply didn't know?
Don't you think it's so irresponsible?
You looked happy.
A wealthy family and wonderful adoptive parents.
You were growing up well, enjoying a happy childhood.
I did not want...
to ruin your happy life.
Your daughter has never once felt happy.
She was always anxious, having to live someone else's life,
and she often felt miserable.
She had to surpass Han Na, her adoptive parents' real daughter.
She thought it was the only way to be loved.
She never once...
lived as Choi Se Gyeong.
So, say this as your answer.
If someone who looks just like me asks you the same question,
tell her this over and over.
"I never once abandoned you."
"You're not Han Na."
"You're my daughter born of love,"
"Choi Se Gyeong."
If you don't tell her,
she'll never know.
That's it, no more.
The rest is up to you people to figure out.
I won't meddle anymore.
I'm afraid something else might change.
I'm afraid I might fail to protect my loved ones, like Yi Chan.
I want to go home now.
(Operating Room, Intensive Care Unit)
Who are you, really?
Tomorrow night, two full moons will rise.
When the two full moons appear in the sky,
the gate that connects the past to the present...
or the present to the future will open.
What does that have to do with me?
Wrap up your journey...
and come to the place where you arrived.
As I had promised,
I'll keep the lights on at La Vida Music.
Oh, right.
I'll also have lavender tea ready as your welcome tea.
Do you think...
I can go back in this situation?
Tomorrow is your only chance to go back.
If you decide to stay,
your life in 2023...
will disappear.
Will you be okay with that?
You do not belong to this world,
so we cannot even predict what kinds of ripple effects...
your existence in this world might bring about.
Are you...
really okay with that?
Why are you doing this to me?
What on earth did I do?
What did I do so wrong...
that I've ended up in such a ridiculous situation?
Whatever you decide,
I truly hope that you make a choice for your own sake.
- Goodbye.
- Don't hang up.
I told you not to hang up.
I told you not to hang up! I'm not done talking yet!
Hey, Eun Gyeol.
They just finished Yi Chan's surgery.
How did it go? Did the surgery go well?
Yes, it went well.
They said he'd be okay, for sure.
He'll soon be moved to a regular ward.
(Yeonnam Hospital)
Yi Chan.
Dad.
I'm sorry, Dad.
Had I not come here,
this wouldn't have happened.
Dad.
The fact that you can't hear wasn't the reason I said nothing to you.
I didn't say...
those mean things to you because I hated you.
I love you very much, Dad.
So please...
Please open your eyes.
There's something I must tell you.
You can't keep on sleeping like this.
Also...
I might have to...
go back soon.
(Yeonnam Hospital)
Yi Chan.
Hey, something's wrong with me.
I can't hear anything.
I can't even hear my own voice.
Gosh, Ms. Go.
You'll trip and fall. Slow down.
My gosh.
We can't keep this a secret forever.
It's not like he can go home in a day or two.
Oh, dear. My goodness.
Do you recognize me?
Ms. Go, I told you that he was totally fine mentally.
Who am I? Answer my question at once.
You're my grandma.
Do you hear my voice?
I'll be home soon. Why did you come here?
I was happy, thinking I could take a break from your nagging.
Do you hear my voice?
I'm sorry, Grandma.
You said you adored me because I was healthy physically and mentally.
What should I do now?
To make up for what happened,
I'll try to cultivate a more beautiful heart.
I'll focus on building that muscle.
Gosh, my sweetheart.
They say all good things must come to an end.
How could something like this happen?
I've never seen anyone kinder than my grandson.
What did my sweet grandson do to deserve this?
I can't believe this.
Oh, dear.
Grandma, why are you crying?
It's not like I'm dead.
I was always so busy cooking for others...
that I never once properly fed you or clothed you.
You never even experienced your parents' love,
and yet I always picked on you.
I've never once warmly embraced you.
What should we do now?
Grandma.
- Gosh, what should we do?
- Grandma.
Let's ask them to carefully examine you,
from head to toe.
If they say they can't fix it,
I will give you my ears.
If it is a new heart that you need, I will give you mine.
If you need new eyes, I will give you both of my eyes.
Oh, dear. What should we do? You poor thing.
My sweetheart, what are we going to do?
Gosh, my sweet grandson.
I will fix you. Don't you worry.
I will give you my heart and my eyes too.
I'll give you whatever you need.
Hey, Eun Gyeol.
What's going on? Where are you going?
To find the scumbag who made Yi Chan like that.
If the police can't find the driver, I will.
I will find him and kill him.
They already caught the driver, so calm down.
They caught him this morning.
I just checked. I'm coming from the police station.
But the thing is,
I think it's better that we don't tell Yi Chan or his grandmother.
What do you mean?
Why?
Is it someone we know?
Yes.
It's Yoon Ju Yeop, Chung Ah's stepbrother.
Do you want to tag along on my upcoming business trip?
I'm going to a place with many art galleries, so you'll have fun.
Paintings.
You like them, right?
Did I get it wrong?
("The Most Beautiful Language: Lovely Sign Language")
You can look...
at paintings,
and I'll make some time...
so we can take a trip...
I really want you to see it.
See what?
Chung Ah's smile.
She has such a pretty smile.
I'll join you.
I told you. It wasn't intentional.
He suddenly jumped in front of my car.
I meant to hit the brakes, but I was so startled...
that I stepped on the accelerator by mistake.
How many times do I have to tell you?
That's really odd.
The skid marks on the road tell a different story.
What are you, a psychic?
Do cops have the ability to commune with asphalt or something?
You'd better strategize wisely.
It'll be considered attempted murder if we prove that it was intentional.
I told you it wasn't intentional...
Forget it.
I won't say a word more until my attorney gets here, so...
It was intentional.
You saw me and drove straight toward me.
Stop. We're at a police station now, Eun Gyeol.
Thank you for letting him know and telling him to stop.
You tried to kill me.
You were trying to kill me,
but Yi Chan got hit because he tried to save me!
Darn you, seriously!
You're falsely accusing me. Do you have evidence?
I will kill you.
If you bribe your way out of this, I'll follow you...
to the end of the world and punish you myself.
I will do anything and everything you're imagining and are afraid of.
I will latch on to you like a leech and kill you slowly.
Don't complicate things. Let's get out of here, okay?
I will kill you.
I won't leave you alone until the day you die!
I will kill you!
Darn it.
When will my attorney get here?
Can I make a phone call?
This is a democratic country. You can let me do that much, right?
The two moons will rise tonight.
Master called you too, right?
This is where we stop. We shouldn't meddle anymore.
We must go back.
Not now.
If we don't go back today, we'll be trapped here forever.
Until I make sure everything can go back to the way it used to be,
I will not go back.
But how?
How will you undo something that already happened?
By going back to the past?
And you'll travel further back in time if something else changes?
Come to your senses.
You must go back to 2023.
How could I go back?
Knowing my dad's life got ruined because of me...
and that I couldn't change anything.
I should've just let things unfold the way they were supposed to.
I shouldn't have stepped in.
What do you mean you changed nothing?
You saved me,
and you rescued Chung Ah.
Yi Chan, I'm going on a trip with my dad.
I'm just tagging along on his work trip,
but this is my first trip with him, so I'm a little excited.
(Subway Safety Maintenance to Be Strengthened)
Thanks.
I owe it all to you.
Knowing that someone's always on my side makes me very happy.
It makes me feel safe and gives me courage.
For some reason, it helps me become stronger.
I hope I can do the same for you.
To Yi Chan, who's always on my side.
From Chung Ah, who's always on your side.
Please find a good school overseas for Chung Ah.
Sure thing, sir.
I heard about Gallaudet University. It's a college for the deaf.
Look into their admission requirements as well.
Even college?
Chung Ah...
will not come back once she leaves Korea this time.
Please don't tell Chung Ah.
Well understood, sir.
Also, we'll cover Yi Chan's medical expenses and all his tuition fees...
until he graduates from college.
I'll proceed accordingly, sir.
As for the case involving Ju Yeop,
I will not cooperate no matter what the legal team...
asks me to do.
Ms. Im Ji Mi.
We're from the National Tax Service.
You've just been banned from leaving the country due to a tax audit.
I'm sure all your efforts...
changed the situation for the better.
So...
let's stop here...
and now return to the world where we belong.
But...
I cannot leave.
Would you be happy if your life in 2023 completely disappeared?
My dad is in utter despair now.
I can't ditch him and run away alone.
Now, I understand what Eun Ho meant.
Back then, I couldn't fully understand him...
as I didn't know much sign language,
but I get it now.
The reason...
Eun Ho didn't tell you about your dad's accident.
When will you show your brother?
When the burden on his shoulders becomes lighter.
Right now, it seems a little too heavy.
Put down the burden already. It's not your burden to carry.
You forced yourself to take on the burden.
Do you think it made them happy?
No.
On the contrary, it made them worry, and it made them sad.
They worried that you'd become more miserable because of them.
No one can live your life for you.
Let Yi Chan in 1995...
figure things out on his own.
Believe in Yi Chan.
Yi Chan and Chung Ah exist in 2023 too.
Eun Ho is there too.
There are people who are waiting for you.
And I live in that world too.
I will go back.
Pack your things and meet me at my place at 9pm.
I'll be waiting for you.
You could flip a coin.
(Nationwide Cello Competition, 1st Place Winner Choi Se Gyeong)
(Watermelon Sugar)
("A Song for You")
It's been a while, Mr. Viva.
I thought I'd never see you again.
But we meet again like this.
Oh, my. Brava.
I thought you just felt a little lost for a short while.
But you were a lot more rebellious than I thought.
What are you?
Who are you?
Me? I am...
On Eun Yu, Choi Se Gyeong's daughter from the future.
I must be going crazy. I'm losing my sanity.
I've lost my mind.
Hey, wait.
Just one moment.
Since I've already revealed myself, let me say a few more things.
Keep that rebellious spirit and tell your adoptive parents...
that you can't replace Han Na.
And you had to pluck up your courage to meet your birth father,
so go back and ask him.
"Why did you abandon me?"
Then he'll answer your question as if he's been waiting for it.
And just like you can't replace Han Na,
I can't live your life for you, Mom.
So, go ahead and live your life, Mom.
You deserve it.
Why? Because...
you're charming and cool just as you are.
Oh, you can run away now.
I'm busy too.
I'll tidy up here,
so don't worry.
You cleaned my room for me for years, Mom.
This has to be a dream. I'm seeing things.
This can't be real.
I can't see you out!
Bye, Mom.
We'll meet again 28 years later.
Ask away.
It's written all over your face.
Your mind is full of questions now.
I debated whether I should flip a coin before coming here.
You read my mind.
A coin?
Someone once advised me...
to try flipping a coin...
if I ever had to make a difficult decision.
How about I give you this instead of a coin?
("A Song for You")
Se Gyeong told me to burn it,
but I really think you should take a listen.
The song is great. Make sure you listen to it to the end.
("A Song for You")
Did I ever tell you?
My parents are deaf.
I have a brother who's a year older than me.
He's also deaf.
A child like me...
who was born to deaf parents...
is called a CODA.
"CODA?"
People who do music all understand what this means.
It's like a code word.
It's called a coda.
When you see a coda near the end of a song,
you know you should get ready to wrap it up beautifully.
That's why I came to see you.
I think it's time...
to get ready to wrap things up beautifully.
Are you going somewhere?
Thank you for everything.
This time, I wanted...
to say my final goodbye to you in person.
What's with you? Why are you acting like I'll never see you again?
Take care of your health.
Especially your heart.
And make sure you reconcile with your daughter.
Later on...
Many years later,
if you see a boy crying alone in front of your shop,
give him a glass of milk instead of hot cocoa.
He likes milk better than hot cocoa.
I'm the front man of the band, First Love Memory Manipulators.
My name is Ha Yi Chan.
- Dad?
- Why do you keep calling me "Dad?"
Pass!
Welcome to First Love Memory Manipulators.
Yes.
Special thanks to Ha Eun Gyeol.
Thanks to you, I was able to complete this song.
Looking back, I realized...
that this song wasn't the only thing you helped me complete.
I will make your youth twinkle just like your wish.
When I wanted something,
when I felt like I lacked something, when I was in despair...
(Baekwang High School's Sparkling Festival)
And even at my most radiant moments,
you were always there with me.
You lied to me that you were my son.
I'm your son from the future.
You're my dad.
But you know what?
For some reason, I felt as though you were like my father.
Even though I have never experienced a father's love,
I got to experience something similar thanks to you.
Son, thank you.
But...
in my next life, I'll be born as your father.
Hey, Yi Chan!
Don't make me set the table twice. Come out and eat now!
Are you going back?
I saw your reflection on the window...
and the sad look on your face before bidding farewell.
That was my Sherlock Holmes moment.
I'm sorry.
Where are you going?
Home? Abroad to study?
Or the future?
You said you were from the future.
I'm really sorry.
I'm just curious.
What happens to me in the future?
Do I even go to college?
What about the band? Do I keep playing?
Will I...
be able to hear then?
Will I have stopped putting my grandma through a hard time...
and become a good grandson,
leading a proper life?
You will have a good life.
Your life will twinkle more than anyone's life.
Remember what I told you before?
Your wife will love you.
Your children will respect you.
You will become an excellent father.
That will be your future.
Your weakness will make you unique.
You will turn every hardship...
into the story of a hero.
- So...
- What are you saying?
I can't hear you at all.
So...
Keep your promise.
Be strong and overcome this.
Make sure to become my father.
You listened to it.
This isn't your fault.
Accidents are just accidents.
I will be miserable for some time now.
But I won't be in despair, thinking my life is ruined.
So go.
Don't even look back, and leave.
Go.
When you can finally get rid of that guilty look on your face,
come back to see me.
(I have no doubt that you will come.)
I have no doubt that you will come.
I thought about waiting for you a little longer.
But I have a long way ahead of you, so I'll get going first.
See you after 28 years. Metaphor On.
What? What's wrong with this?
Gosh.
Oh, no.
Excuse me!
Is anyone out here? I need help!
Gosh. Please help me!
(Used Books, The Day)
I want my guitar back.
I guess you want to change your life,
not other people's lives this time.
Drink this while I go and look for it.
The lavender in the tea was harvested personally by me.
It will help you calm down and sleep better.
Here's a thing about life.
It may not give you everything you want.
But it does hide a small present for you from time to time.
I hope you can endure...
the cruel hardship life throws your way.
So you can receive the present life has tucked away.
To you...
and everyone you wanted to protect,
viva la Vida.
Long live life.
What is it? Was there a problem with the way I stored it?
Who on earth are you?
Even if I were to ask you that, you won't give me an answer.
Just think of it as a joke from the deity.
Life is filled with all kinds of metaphors.
Interpretation is solely up to the receiver.
There are no right answers.
- I don't follow you.
- Okay.
But thanks for the tea.
You're an artist. You should know what a metaphor is.
When you find yourself in need of an answer, flip a coin.
It was nice meeting you, kiddo.
What happened?
This is the guest room of the Jinsung family.
Am I dreaming?
Or is this real?
What did he put in the lavender tea? Come on.
- I'm sorry. I didn't get that.
- Gosh, that startled me.
What year is it now?
It's 2023.
Then did I come back to the present?
Then why am I here?
What do you mean you changed nothing?
You rescued Chung Ah.
Believe in Yi Chan.
Yi Chan and Chung Ah exist in 2023 too.
Eun Ho is there too.
There are people who are waiting for you.
And I live in that world too.
(On Eun Yu)
The number you dialled does not exist.
Who are you?
Did you get the wrong house?
It was definitely this house.
Do you know where the previous tenants moved?
Nonsense.
I built this house five years ago and moved in here.
- There were no previous tenants.
- Then...
Eun Yu's history has changed.
No way. Did she fail to come back from 1995?
(Jun Hyung of SPINE9)
- Hey!
- Where are you right now?
Do you know how long I've been waiting for you at the salon?
Forget it. I'm on my way to pick you up. Wait at your house.
What? Hello?
The salon?
What salon?
Excuse me.
You're him, right? Ha Eun Gyeol of SPINE9?
- It's him! This is awesome!
- No way!
Gosh. Take his pictures.
Eun Gyeol.
Can you give me a strand of your hair?
My hair?
- Two, please.
- What?
I just need two strands of your hair.
- Eun Gyeol!
What's happening? Why are they following me?
Am I famous or something?
- Eun Gyeol!
- We love you!
- Oh, no! He left!
Gosh. Thank you...
Guys.
You guys look so fancy now.
People might think you're artists of MJ Entertainment.
Look at this sly punk.
He's trying to weasel his way out of this one.
Forget it.
We'll go on a tour during your school break.
Did you get their permission?
A tour?
Are we going on a travel tour as a group?
A travel tour, my foot.
I'm talking about our tour abroad!
Our tour abroad?
Us?
We'll perform on stage as Yoon Dong Jin's support band.
I told you to get permission from your parents for the tour.
Did you just come back from your previous life or something?
He's just sorry because he's late.
First of all, Soo Ji will come to our event for us.
As soon as we arrive, get your makeup done and put on...
Our event?
What event?
- What's wrong with you?
(SPINE9's Celebratory Performance for the Launch of Goliath)
So let me get this straight.
We're the artists of MJ Entertainment...
and Jinsung Musical Instruments' endorsers as well.
They're throwing a launch party for Goliath today.
So we are going to perform at the party.
I'm also the grandson of the Jinsung family?
You're back to your senses, right?
Then can you please get to the green room already?
Let's go. Come on.
What took you so long?
Eun Ho.
I missed you, Eun Ho!
What about your suit?
Eun Ho.
You need to meet Dad's friends.
I told you to put that on.
I had never...
considered you my burden.
Is that so?
I considered you my burden many times, actually.
Like now.
Where are Mom and Dad?
- Thank you.
- She thanks you.
(I hope you have a nice time here.)
Thanks to you, I'm already having a nice time.
Our country has improved a lot, hasn't it?
(Yoon Chung Ah)
(Yoon Chung Ah, businesswoman)
(Graduated from Model Secondary School)
(Yoon Chung Ah, achievements)
("Chairwoman Yoon Volunteers on Sign Language Day")
Well done, Chung Ah.
I mean it.
I'm so proud of you.
Buttering me up won't make any difference.
I don't agree with your dad.
Don't forget that I let you play in the band...
because you promised to go to college.
The moment your grades go down, your tour abroad...
Go back to your positions.
Smile.
- Step back.
- Hold on!
- Ma'am!
- Look over here, please!
- Hello.
- You're here.
- Nice to see you.
Have you been well?
Who are they?
They're Dad's high school friends. They played in the band together.
Have you been well?
Was there a lot of traffic?
(Luckily, no.)
Ma Joo is running late because of work.
You look so gorgeous today.
Just today?
Just today.
Yi Chan was the one who cut all ties with his friend.
When he saw his friends, his heart ached a bit...
and he missed those days.
Whenever they saw him, they seemed sad,
and watching their sad faces was painful.
(Contemporary Lineup of New Custom Electric Guitars)
(When will Dad get here?)
The ambitious series of Jinsung Musical Instruments.
I now present you Goliath S.
I would also like to introduce someone to you.
He's the driving force behind the birth of Goliath.
Please welcome Director Ha Yi Chan with a big round of applause.
(Director Ha Yi Chan of Guitar Business Department)
(Graduated from Gallaudet University, USA)
(Jinsung Musical Instruments)
My initial dream was to become part of a cool band,
dominate the world with our music,
and win over the pretty girl.
I had lost my hearing from an accident.
So my dream was shattered to pieces back then.
When I first lost my hearing,
I was very scared.
I was afraid.
I was furious.
Hopelessness swallowed me.
So there was a time I couldn't talk at all.
However,
I gave up on giving up...
because as I had lived 18 years of my life...
in the world with sounds,
so I was able to remember sounds.
I was also able to imagine them.
Afterwards, I had lived 28 years of my life...
in the world without sounds.
So I was certain that I'd be able to make the most beautiful...
and sought-after sound.
In the end,
I had won over the pretty girl.
- What? Come on.
- Gosh.
As for my dream of world domination,
I believe that Goliath will achieve it in my place.
(Jinsung Musical Instruments)
You look amazing!
Nice!
This is all.
Looking at your faces,
I'm certain Goliath played some beautiful sounds.
He did!
Goodness.
Now, I will exit the stage...
with a sense of reassurance.
Thank you.
Gosh. That punk. He and his showmanship.
Ma Joo.
Look at this brat.
You call your boss by his name?
Am I your friend?
I'm sorry.
Hurry up and run to get ready for the concert, will you?
I won't go easy on you just because you're my friend's son.
Yes, sir. I'll get going.
Okay.
You saw it, right?
I told you.
I'm not going to feel despair, thinking that my life is ruined.
So don't look back and just go.
When you don't make that guilty face anymore,
come back to meet me again.
How about that?
Are you ready to meet me?
My son. Wasn't I amazing today?
Thank you.
For keeping the promise.
Now, it's my turn to become amazing.
You can look forward to it.
("A Song for You")
Tonight
I'm not scared
No obstacles
Can stand in our way anymore
All right
I'll tell you no matter what
My heart is starting to beat
- Louder now - Let's go!
Step one, even if I fall down,
Step two, I will get up twice
Yes, don't stop, I can fly away
Keep on knocking, and when the door opens,
Then the story about the two of us
Will unfold on this vast sea
Reach out your hands, higher
You can almost touch it
Let's follow our dreams
Keep on knocking, and when the door opens,
Don't you think we were slightly better than them?
Right. And we looked better when we were younger.
Yes. We should...
- be really honest.
- Yes.
By the way,
don't you think Eun Gyeol looks like someone?
I feel like I can remember, but I can't. It's driving me crazy.
He definitely reminds me of someone. Don't you think so?
- Encore.
- Do you want an encore?
- Yes.
- Encore.
Then let's do it right...
If we don't go back today, we'll be trapped here forever.
Please.
Please show up.
It's been a while, Eun Gyeol.
Has it been 28 years?
I thought you couldn't come back.
Right. I almost couldn't come back.
Why did you run away when you came?
I didn't run away.
I was fishing.
So that I can be with you without anyone else.
I guess it's a very nice bait. You took it so quickly.
(Epilogue)
Hello? Is anyone here?
Can anybody help me?
Gosh.
Excuse me.
Do you want to get on?
I made it.
You're back.
I mean, you told me to come.
Can I drink this?
I feel better now.
Hearing that you feel better now,
I guess you gave up on that creative suicide method.
It's not because of you. So you don't have to feel proud.
Oh, right. Master.
Hurry up and just give my cello back.
Already?
You're rushing it too much.
Take a seat and calm down. Let's have a conversation.
I'm a little busy.
I want to see how my mom is doing.
I have questions for my dad too.
And I promised to meet someone.
Are you not going to give it to me? I don't have time.
Here.
Here you go.
Thank you for the travel, Grandpa.
For the one-dollar bills you gave only to me.
For letting me meet my mom who is the same age as me.
For all the good friends I made. For everything.
I'll be doing well with my mom when I go back.
So don't worry too much.
We'll keep arguing, though.
I'll get going then.
I'll live a good life there.
I was so happy that I could meet you.
Bye.
Viva la Vida. Long live life.
(Cameo appearance: Ryu Su Young, Song Chang Eui, and Zin Tai Hyun)
(The soundtrack "Story About You and Me" by wYte is released.)
(Thank you for watching Twinkling Watermelon.)
(Twinkling Watermelon)